So, Zekken shows up at 3 o 'clock
on this island on Floor 24. Mm-hmm.
Then I'll see you guys
there tomorrow at 2.30.
You got it! I can't wait!
This will be so much fun!
Yeah, it will! Ha, yeah!
The Berserk Healer's gonna get unleashed!
Daddy, you have something
on your face! Huh? For real?
Yes, it's covered in ink! You're kidding!
See you guys tomorrow!
Yeah, see ya!
I don't know.
I've never been in the sky,
but I haven't been in the sky,
but I haven't been able to reach my feet.
I've never seen the cold,
but I've never seen the rain.
I don't regret anything,
but the sound of the sound
is coming from the sky.
This story is the beginning of the song.
We are connected to
the end of the journey.
You can create the world of the future.
We are in the sky in the sky.
Two pieces of the dream.
One piece of the dream.
Oh?
Good night, Miss Sara.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry you had to work so late.
Not at all, really.
Just doing my job, miss.
Do you know if my mother
and brother are home yet?
Koichi wrote a phone to say he
won't be in until late tonight.
And your mother is waiting
in the dining room.
Oh, thank you.
Have a good night, Miss Sara.
You're late.
Next time, I want you
here five minutes early.
Yes, ma 'am.
It looks good.
I assume you were using that thing again?
Yes.
My friends and I were doing
our homework together.
Unless you actually physically do your
homework, you won't learn a thing.
But we all live so far
away from each other.
It's more convenient
for us to meet in-game.
It hardly qualifies as meeting
if you're using that toy.
Besides, doing your homework
is not a team activity.
If you're with your friends,
you'll just fool around.
Asuna, you don't have time
to play around anymore.
You're two years behind everyone else.
You should be studying as hard as you
can to make up for all that lost time.
But I am studying hard.
Didn't you see my grades
for the second semester?
I left them on your desk.
Yes, I saw them.
But grades from a school like
that are suspect at best.
They're not suspect?
Yes, Will.
For your next trimester, I've
decided to hire you a tutor.
And not one of those virtual
ones everyone's going on about.
Someone who'll come to the house.
But don't I get to have any say in it?
Have a look at this.
A transfer exam study guide?
I know someone on the
board of directors there.
After some discussion,
I convinced them to let you take an exam
to transfer into their senior class.
It's a proper high school,
not some makeshift study hall.
And since it's credit-based,
I'm sure you'll be able to
graduate after the first trimester.
If you do, you'll be back
on track for college.
Wait, hold on!
You can't just make a
decision like this without me.
I happen to like the school I'm in.
The teachers there are great.
I can learn there just
as much as anywhere.
I don't have to change schools.
I've done my research, you know.
And believe me, that place you're
attending can hardly be called a school.
The curriculum is slapdash
and the classes are a joke.
Even the faculty is substandard.
They're a bunch of losers with
no real credentials to speak of.
Don't say that.
They claim they're helping the students
who fell behind because of that accident.
It's all a lie.
They just want all the
children who've spent the last
two years killing each other
in one convenient place.
So they can monitor them.
It's more like an asylum than a school.
Did you forget, Mother?
I spent two years killing other kids, too.
All the friends you
had back in junior high
are studying to get
into college this year.
They're leaving you behind.
Doesn't that bother you?
Not at all.
If it takes an extra year or two,
it won't make much of a difference.
Besides, I might not
want to go to college.
Ridiculous.
I won't entertain such talk.
You're far too gifted.
And your father and I have gone to
great lengths to nurture your talents.
I hope you appreciate that.
I do, but shouldn't I get to
have a say in my own future?
Sure, I might not know what
kind of career I want right now,
but I'm close to finding out.
If I stay in my school for another year,
it will help me make that decision.
No matter how long you stay at a place
like that, it'll just limit your options.
Look, try to understand.
I don't want you to make a wrong
turn now and regret it later.
I just want you to have
a good life and find
yourself a good career
you can be proud of.
So that boy you forced me
to meet on New Year's Day,
that was you trying to
help me with my career?
You should have heard him.
He was talking like we were
already engaged or something.
You're the one who's limiting my
options, not me and not my school.
Marriage is part of your career.
If you marry beneath you, or marry
poor, I guarantee you'll regret it.
You won't have the means to pursue
whatever it is you really want to do.
That's why I think Yu-Yu
would be an excellent choice.
His family owns a small regional bank.
Those are much more stable than some
mega-bank run by a board of directors.
Your last choice wasn't very good.
Did you forget how he made me, and
I don't know how many others suffer?
Nobuyuki Tsuko nearly bankrupted Ragout.
He was your choice, mother.
Enough, young lady!
I don't want to hear about
him in this house again.
And you're wrong.
It wasn't my choice, it was your father's.
He suggested that crook
marry into this family.
He's never been a good judge of character.
But don't worry.
Yuya might lack initiative,
but he seems stable.
And stability is the
cornerstone of marriage.
I don't care.
I have no intention to date or marry him.
I choose who I'll marry.
Fine, as long as the man you choose is
from a good family and is worthy of you.
However, a boy like that, your little
friend from school, is not worthy.
You had him investigated?
Of course I did.
Try to understand, your father and I
only want what's best for you in life.
You have the potential
to do whatever you want,
as long as you make the right choices.
I need time to think about transferring.
Keep in mind, the deadline's next week.
Don't forget, and after
you fill out the form,
make three copies and leave
them in my office on my desk.
Mother.
What is it?
Even though they're gone, you're still
ashamed of Grandma and Grandpa, aren't you?
You're angry you weren't born
into a rich, important family.
Asuna!
Come back here right now!
Kirito!
Hey, about that questionnaire.
Have you figured out
what you want to do yet?
I guess, if anything, I want to go from
playing games to being a creator. A creator?
What, for games?
No, not for games.
I want to make a human-machine interface
to replace the full-dive tech we use now.
I've been going to all these tech
forums to learn more about it,
but it's a heck of a lot
of information to absorb.
I want to be with Kirito
and go after the same dream.
But now...
You sure are strong,
way stronger than I am.
I'm not strong at all.
In that world, I was a warrior.
But here, Lightning Flash Asuna of
the Knights of the Blood Oath is gone.
In the real world, I
don't have any real power.
It's rare for you to be so
punctual, don't you think?
It happens sometimes.
Hey, you remember?
You know, that one day you came to my
place in Selmburg and I made you dinner?
Hate to say it, but my memory's
about as good as my punctuality.
What?
Yeah, I remember that day
like it was yesterday.
Really? Of course.
Let's see that's the day
I got a super rare food
item right and you made
an awesome stew out of it
That was some tasty meat.
I'm never gonna forget that day
You don't remember anything
except that stupid dinner?
It's almost time I better get over there!
Asuna be careful with second.
Well, it's like, Zekin's really
strong. Just saying. Don't you worry.
Listen, the others already
told me everything.
Yep, they even told me about how you lost.
I still can't believe it.
Oh, by the way,
Leafa said in the middle of your duel
with Zekken you stopped fighting to talk.
What'd you talk about?
Well, actually I asked
a question. What about?
I got a weird vibe, so I asked.
You're full-time in this
world, aren't you, Zekken?
And then, for an answer, I got a
sly grin and a mega-fast attack.
I'd never seen anything move that fast.
What did you mean by
full-time in this world?
Is that the same thing
as being a heavy user?
Uh-uh.
Zekin's way different than your
average everyday hardcore gamer.
It felt like...
like they were a sort of product of
the full-dive environment itself.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
In a way, it's probably better you don't.
The best way to explain it
is for you to experience it.
Every time we turn around, you're
always pawing at each other.
Sorry to interrupt your little love fest,
but there's a duel that's
supposed to be happening.
Yeah!
I know, I was on my way.
I yield! I quit! Resign!
Hi-ya!
That's 67 wins in a row!
Second undefeated!
Excuse me, Liz. What?
You asked me seconds a girl!
I didn't!
I could have sworn! I did!
You didn't!
And you!
I have a feeling! I
know! Why you lost? Now!
No!
You're wrong!
I didn't go easy on her!
Because she's a girl!
I was going full out!
I swear!
Halfway through our duel! Anyway!
Whatever!
So, uh, is there anyone else out there
want to take me on today? You're up.
Go on, get her.
Wait, I gotta psych myself up first.
Oh, please, once you cross swords with
her, believe me, you'll get psyched up.
Go on, get in there!
Hey, what's up? You next?
Oh, uh, hi.
I guess I am.
Awesome!
So, uh, does anything go
in this duel? Of course!
You can use magic or
items, whatever you want.
I'm only gonna use my sword, though.
Oh, wait. Almost forgot.
You want to fight on the
ground or in the air?
Is ether okay? Mm-hmm.
Let's duel on the ground then
you got it jumping's allowed,
but no using your wings, okay?
I don't know.
She is strong, but if I gave up now,
I'd ruin my reputation as a Swordsman.
In that world, I was a warrior.
But here?
Ah!
Mm…
Uh-oh!
Got her!
She saw my quadruple pain?
No way!
I won't lose!
Is this the Head combo?
Her original sword skill!
If I'm going to lose, it might as well
be to something as awesome as that!
That was an awesome fight, girl!
You're definitely the one!
Uh, what?
Aren't we gonna finish the duel?
I totally seen enough to
know you got what it takes.
But if you want, we can keep going.
I've been looking for someone
who could go the distance.
At last, I found you.
Mommy?
Asuna, where are you going? Asuna!
I picked ya, cause you're
the only one who can help us!
Help? With what?
Thank you.
I don't want to go.
I tend to be lazy to call.
You are sure?
I'm never wrong.
I have to be close to you.
I didn't see light.
I'm not okay.
I'm never wrong. I'm never wrong.
I want to see how many times I can hear?
Next time, the Sleeping Knights.